https://solarcsystems.com/en/information/privacy-policy/

0 Items
INFORMATIONFAQPsoriasis InfoVitiligo InfoEczema InfoVitamin D InfoUnderstanding UVB NarrowbandUV WavebandsUVB and Skin CancerHome-Use StudyPrescriptionsPhototherapy CalendarsPRODUCTSSelection GuideSolRx E-SeriesSolRx 1000-SeriesSolRx 500-SeriesSolRx 100-SeriesUV Bulbs/LampsUV Eyewear550CR Clinic RatedORDERINGSolRx StoreInsurance TipsOrdering TipsDownload CentreHospitals & ClinicsInternationalDistributorsWarranty / ReturnsPATIENT STORIESOUR STORYCONTACT
Select Page
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Solarc Systems Inc. collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.solarcsystems.com and www.solarcsystems.com websites (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Solarc Systems Inc..Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, registers on the site, places an order, subscribes to the newsletter, responds to a survey, fills out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance the User’s experience. The User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.Solarc Systems Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support your needs more efficiently.To personalize the User’s experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To process payments: We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order but, only to provide the service relating to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If the User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or Users may contact us via our Site or any other way.We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Site. Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.Solarc Systems Inc. will not share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.Google AdsenseSome of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.Compliance with children’s online privacy protection actProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.Changes to this privacy policySolarc Systems Inc. has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Solarc Systems Inc.
1515 Snow Valley
Barrie, ON L9X 1K3
(705) 739-8279
info@solarcsystems.com
www.solarcsystems.comThis document was last updated January 2016.MORE INFOContact UsRegulatory InformationISO Certified Quality SystemTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyWarranty & Returned Goods PolicyMercury WarningUVB and Skin CancerYour Story
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
YouTube
Selection GuideSolRx 1000-SeriesSolRx 500-SeriesSolRx 100-SeriesUV Replacement BulbsMy AccountCartCopyright © 1995 - 2020 Solarc Systems Inc.
All rights reserved
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance the User’s experience. The User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.OkPrivacy policy
